[
    {
        "question":"Anagram of TRREEESSSS",
        "answers":["RESTRESSES"]
    }
    , {
        "question":"Anagram of TRRPPPEEEE",
        "answers":["PEPPERTREE"]
    }
    , {
        "question":"Anagram of RNNSSSEEEE",
        "answers":["SERENENESS"]
    }
    , {
        "question":"Anagram of VLLSSSEEEE",
        "answers":["SLEEVELESS"]
    }
    , {
        "question":"Anagram of VNNSSSEEEE",
        "answers":["EVENNESSES"]
    }
    , {
        "question":"Anagram of KNNSSSEEEE",
        "answers":["KEENNESSES"]
    }
    , {
        "question":"Anagram of BMMRRREEEE",
        "answers":["REMEMBERER"]
    }
    , {
        "question":"Anagram of DIIEEESSSS",
        "answers":["DISSEISEES"]
    }
    , {
        "question":"Anagram of ERRUUUSSSS",
        "answers":["SUSURRUSES"]
    }
    , {
        "question":"Anagram of HAAEEEDDDD",
        "answers":["DEADHEADED"]
    }
    , {
        "question":"Anagram of ANNEEESSSS",
        "answers":["SANENESSES"]
    }
]